Digital Media Department Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Academics, 2007 December 5-2016 July 17; nam_ua395-1; 50.15 GB 36697 Digital Files
  - Division of Research, 2012 October 24-2015 January 14; nam_ua395-1.7; 194.1 MB 136 Digital Files
    - President: 10/4/05 @ 1:30 PM CC Terrace Lounge Building Manager Mtg digital, 2005 October 14; nam_ua395-1.7_3; 47.0 MB 33 Digital Files
  - Library, 2008 April 29-2014 August 22; nam_ua395-1.8; 564.0 MB 316 Digital Files
    - Alumni Affairs: 9/27/00 @ 10 AM New Library Archives room Group of four alumni working on Veteran's Project digital image, 2000 October 9; nam_ua395-1.8_1; 9.1 MB 14 Digital Files
    - Advancement Events: 4/5/01 @ 11:15 AM Science Library Atrium "Two Millionth Volume" Ceremony digital, 2001 February 13; nam_ua395-1.8_2; 75.1 MB 92 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 10/7/04 @ 1 PM - 3 PM President's Reading Room / Main Library Distinguished Professor Unveiling and reception digital, 2004 October 1; nam_ua395-1.8_3; 55.5 MB 42 Digital Files
    - Advancement Events: 9/30/05 @ 4 PM - 5:30 PM Science Library / Barnes & Noble Room Welcome Reception for Library Dean: Frank D'Andraia digital, 2005 September 22; nam_ua395-1.8_4; 100.6 MB 68 Digital Files
    - President's Office: photo shoot: 9/12/05 @ 12:30 PM CC 375 MidTown Meeting digital, 2005 September 22; nam_ua395-1.8_5; 50.4 MB 32 Digital Files
    - President: 2 PM - 3 PM Cobb Room Main Library (Basement) Library Faculty Meeting digital, 2005 November 16; nam_ua395-1.8_6; 36.7 MB 16 Digital Files
    - President: 11/18/05 @ 12 Noon CC Ballroom Researching New York Conference digital, 2005 November 30; nam_ua395-1.8_7; 222.3 MB 46 Digital Files
    - Event in M.E. Grenander Reading Room, 2009 May 12; nam_ua395-1.8_8; 14.3 MB 6 Digital Files
  - Rockefeller College, 2014 February 4-2016 June 3; nam_ua395-1.9; 6.4 GB 5036 Digital Files
    - Professional Development Program: 10/9/01 @ 11:30 - 2:30 Downtown Campus/ Richardson 3rd Fl PDP Open House digital, 2001 October 8; nam_ua395-1.9_1; 50.8 MB 42 Digital Files
    - Professional Development Program: 10/18/01 @ 1:30 - 4:00 PM Downtown Campus Symposium and reception digital, 2001 October 8; nam_ua395-1.9_2; 131.2 MB 115 Digital Files
    - Professional Development Program: 10/23/01 @ 12 :00 noon Century House - Latham, NY All Staff Day - group photo (approx: 100 people) color film, 2001 October 8; nam_ua395-1.9_3; 38.8 MB 29 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 12/17/02 @ 2:30 PM Milne 317 David McCaffery and Emil Bove digital, 2002 December 25; nam_ua395-1.9_4; 22.4 MB 20 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 5/15/03 @ 3:30 PM Milne rm200 Burton Lecture digital, 2003 May 19; nam_ua395-1.9_5; 21.8 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 5/15/03 @ 3:30 PM Milne rm200 Burton Lecture digital, 2003 May 19; nam_ua395-1.9_6; 23.0 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 5/19/03 @ 3:30 PM pond/Uptown Campus portrait: Julian Zelizer for book cover digital, 2003 June 3; nam_ua395-1.9_7; 16.0 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 5/19/03 @ 3:30 PM pond/Uptown Campus portrait: Julian Zelizer for book cover digital, 2003 June 3; nam_ua395-1.9_8; 16.0 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 11/12/03 @ 5:30 PM Rockefeller College 411 State St. Alumni Awards Ceremony digital / Suzanne Kowala, 2003 November 24; nam_ua395-1.9_9; 336.7 MB 157 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 11/12/03 @ 5:30 PM Rockefeller College 411 State St. Alumni Awards Ceremony digital / Suzanne Kowala, 2003 November 24; nam_ua395-1.9_10; 336.7 MB 157 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/13/04 @ 3:30 PM Draper 105 Burton Lecture and Reception: Alan Hevesi, 2004 May 14; nam_ua395-1.9_11; 60.0 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/13/04 @ 3:30 PM Draper 105 Burton Lecture and Reception: Alan Hevesi, 2004 May 14; nam_ua395-1.9_12; 119.1 MB 88 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/13/04 @ 3:30 PM Draper 105 Burton Lecture and Reception: Alan Hevesi, 2004 May 14; nam_ua395-1.9_13; 60.0 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/13/04 @ 3:30 PM Draper 105 Burton Lecture and Reception: Alan Hevesi, 2004 May 14; nam_ua395-1.9_14; 119.1 MB 88 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; nam_ua395-1.9_15; 150.2 MB 78 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; nam_ua395-1.9_16; 82.2 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; nam_ua395-1.9_17; 79.3 MB 54 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; nam_ua395-1.9_18; 150.2 MB 78 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; nam_ua395-1.9_19; 82.2 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; nam_ua395-1.9_20; 79.3 MB 54 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 11/30/04 @ 5:30 PM - 8:30 PM 411 State St. / Rockefeller Institute Rocefeller College Awards Reception and Program digital, 2004 December 13; nam_ua395-1.9_21; 142.4 MB 96 Digital Files
    - President: 2/17/05 @ 2:30 PM Milne / Rockefeller College Pres. Hall meeting with Rockefeller College Deans and Faculty digital, 2005 March 3; nam_ua395-1.9_22; 30.8 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/2/05 @ 1:30 PM 1 Computer Drive Colonie, NY Albany-Colonie Chamber of Commerce meets President Hall digital, 2005 March 15; nam_ua395-1.9_23; 37.7 MB 28 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 11/28/05 @ 5:30 PM 411 State St. Rockefeller College Awards digital, 2005 November 18; nam_ua395-1.9_24; 958.0 MB 153 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 5/18/06 @ 4 - 5:30 PM Milne 200 Burton Lecture, 2006 May 22; nam_ua395-1.9_25; 271.0 MB 128 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 5/18/06 @ 4 - 5:30 PM Milne 200 Burton Lecture, 2006 May 22; nam_ua395-1.9_26; 271.2 MB 128 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 10/26/06 @ 7:30 - 9:00 PM Alumni House, Uptown Campus for Dessert Reception with the Undergraduates. Photo session: 10/27/06 @ 9:00 11:00 Professional Applications Class, George Education Center Auditorium, East Campus & 10:30-11:30, Doctoral Student Talks, Levitt Room, Downtown Campus, 2006 October 27; nam_ua395-1.9_27; 499.8 MB 253 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: oreintation for new master students on 8/27/07 from 8:30 - 1 p.m., general shots of interaction, go to Joan's office first in Milne 122B., 2007 September 5; nam_ua395-1.9_28; 67.5 MB 171 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 9/20/07 @ 3:30 PM Milne various locations Cover Shot for viewbook, 2007 October 5; nam_ua395-1.9_29; 499.8 MB 359 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 9/20/07 @ 3:30 PM Milne various locations Cover Shot for viewbook, 2007 October 5; nam_ua395-1.9_30; 499.8 MB 359 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: Rockefeller College Awards ceremony & reception on 11/14/07 from 5:30 - 8:00 p.m.at Rockefeller Institute of Government, 411 State St. Posed photos of award recipients and with presenters, also to include candid shots., 2007 November 2; nam_ua395-1.9_31; 95.1 MB 173 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College Awards, 2008 November 14; nam_ua395-1.9_32; 123.2 MB 201 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College Gad Recognition, 2009 May 16; nam_ua395-1.9_33; 106.5 MB 219 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College Commencement 2009, 2009 May 18; nam_ua395-1.9_34; 97.6 MB 170 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College Alumni Awards, 2009 November 20; nam_ua395-1.9_35; 217.0 MB 271 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College Alumni Awards, 2009 November 20; nam_ua395-1.9_36; 217.0 MB 271 Digital Files
    - Dutch Visit Rockefeller College, 2010 March 1; nam_ua395-1.9_37; 33.6 MB 37 Digital Files
    - RockefellerGrad_commencement2010, 2010 May 14; nam_ua395-1.9_38; 162.7 MB 285 Digital Files
    - RockefellerUndergrad_commencement2010, 2010 May 16; nam_ua395-1.9_39; 205.9 MB 289 Digital Files
    - Joseph Zimmerman class, 2010 September 22; nam_ua395-1.9_40; 34.6 MB 102 Digital Files
  - School of Business, 2008 October 16-2015 September 11; nam_ua395-1.10; 9.15 GB 6565 Digital Files
    - Business: 1/18/02 @ 10 AM BA-233 presentations digital, 2002 January 29; nam_ua395-1.10_1; 45.9 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Business: 12/5/02 @ 8:30 AM MBA presentations digital, 2002 December 17; nam_ua395-1.10_2; 113.5 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Business: 12/12/ 02 @ 8:30 AM BA231 MBA presentations digital, 2002 December 17; nam_ua395-1.10_3; 32.9 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Business: 12/5/02 @ 8:30 AM MBA presentations digital, 2002 December 17; nam_ua395-1.10_4; 113.5 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Business: 12/6/02 @ 9:30 AM Pheonix Insurance, E. Greenbush / St. Peter's Hosp, Albany MIS Interns digital, 2002 December 20; nam_ua395-1.10_5; 3.0 MB 9 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/14/03 @ 10:00/10:30 AM CC small fountain group photo digital, 2003 May 13; nam_ua395-1.10_6; 5.9 MB 12 Digital Files
    - Business: 6/11/03 @ 1 PM BA 227 check presentation digital, 2003 June 25; nam_ua395-1.10_7; 5.7 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Business: 6/11/03 @ 1 PM BA 227 check presentation digital, 2003 June 25; nam_ua395-1.10_8; 5.7 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Business: photo session: 2/25/04 @ 11 AM BA-220 recruitment photo with minority students, 2004 February 26; nam_ua395-1.10_9; 36.4 MB 23 Digital Files
    - Business: photo session: 2/25/04 @ 11 AM BA-220 recruitment photo with minority students, 2004 February 26; nam_ua395-1.10_10; 133.3 MB 84 Digital Files
    - Business: photo session: 2/25/04 @ 11 AM BA-220 recruitment photo with minority students, 2004 February 26; nam_ua395-1.10_11; 133.3 MB 84 Digital Files
    - Business: photo session: 2/25/04 @ 11 AM BA-220 recruitment photo with minority students, 2004 February 26; nam_ua395-1.10_12; 36.4 MB 23 Digital Files
    - Business: 4/29/04 @ 11:45 AM Courtyard next to Business School group photo; Business Faculy and MBA students digital, 2004 April 14; nam_ua395-1.10_13; 63.9 MB 46 Digital Files
    - Business: 4/29/04 @ 11:45 AM Courtyard next to Business School group photo; Business Faculy and MBA students digital, 2004 April 14; nam_ua395-1.10_14; 63.9 MB 46 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/11/04 @ 10:30 AM CC Small Fountain area group photo; MBA Grads digital, 2004 May 5; nam_ua395-1.10_15; 11.3 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/11/04 @ 10:30 AM CC Small Fountain area group photo; MBA Grads digital, 2004 May 5; nam_ua395-1.10_16; 11.3 MB 8 Digital Files
    - President: 4/28/04 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom President Ryan's Speech to Faculty digital, 2004 May 13; nam_ua395-1.10_17; 54.2 MB 52 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/4/04 @ Noon BA-233 MBA Presentations / group shot (Sanjay Goel's class) digital, 2004 May 13; nam_ua395-1.10_18; 9.1 MB 6 Digital Files
    - Business: 2/3/05 @ 5 PM NYC School of Business Event digital, 2005 February 7; nam_ua395-1.10_19; 242.0 MB 186 Digital Files
    - Business: 2/11/05 @ 10:50 AM BA 229 Finance Dept Faculty digital, 2005 February 18; nam_ua395-1.10_20; 21.3 MB 13 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/4/05 @ 3 PM CC west lounge Student Association greets President Hall digital, 2005 February 18; nam_ua395-1.10_21; 99.4 MB 65 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/5/05 @ 1 PM RACC Hall of Fame Room Executive Board greets President Hall digital, 2005 February 21; nam_ua395-1.10_22; 106.2 MB 45 Digital Files
    - Business: 4/6/05 @ 11:30 AM BA 220 plaque unveiling digital, 2005 April 12; nam_ua395-1.10_23; 31.2 MB 25 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/4/05 @ 11:30 AM School of Business Awards Luncheon digital, 2005 April 21; nam_ua395-1.10_24; 124.3 MB 85 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/4/05 @ 6:30 PM CESTM MBA Research Forum digital, 2005 April 21; nam_ua395-1.10_25; 54.6 MB 18 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/9/05 @ 10 AM Draper 113 Pres Hall meets College of Info Science digital, 2005 April 22; nam_ua395-1.10_26; 32.9 MB 25 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/11/05 @ 10:30 AM IT Services IT Suite LC Pres Hall tours IT Services digital, 2005 April 25; nam_ua395-1.10_27; 46.7 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/11/05 @ noon Prez Rez Pine Hills Neighborhood Assoc. Lunch digital, 2005 April 25; nam_ua395-1.10_28; 26.3 MB 14 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/11/05 @ 10 AM CC Assembly Hall MBA class photo digital, 2005 May 4; nam_ua395-1.10_29; 19.9 MB 12 Digital Files
    - Business: 10/20/05 @ 5:30 - 7:30 PM Albany Marriott Wolf Rd. Business Alumni Networking event digital, 2005 August 5; nam_ua395-1.10_30; 215.7 MB 141 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 9/15/05 @ 5:45 PM SS-131 Marketing Class w/ FBI client liaison digital, 2005 September 23; nam_ua395-1.10_31; 65.2 MB 46 Digital Files
    - President: 10/11/05 @ 10:30 AM Standish Room Check Presentation / School of Business digital, 2005 October 25; nam_ua395-1.10_32; 47.8 MB 19 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 10/17/05 @ 11 am Standish Room Norm Snyder gift announcement / School of Business\ digital, 2005 October 31; nam_ua395-1.10_33; 76.3 MB 31 Digital Files
    - President: 10/17/05 @ Noon NYS Assembly Bldg Pres Hall and Hearing for Higher Education digital, 2005 November 1; nam_ua395-1.10_34; 116.9 MB 68 Digital Files
    - Business: 11/10/05 @ 5:30 PM - 7:30 PM UBS Investment Bank / 299 Park Ave (27th Fl. Corner of Park and 49th St. NYC Women's Networking Reception NYC digital, 2005 November 17; nam_ua395-1.10_35; 1.0 GB 152 Digital Files
    - UAF: 12/9/05 @ 7:30 AM Ft. Orange Club Albany School of Business: Vision for the Future digital, 2005 November 29; nam_ua395-1.10_36; 134.9 MB 46 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/4/06 @ 5 PM RACC Big Purple Growl and Ferocious Feast, 2006 February 20; nam_ua395-1.10_37; 225.8 MB 247 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/15/06 @ 1:30 PM BA- HR Lab 2nd Fl Prof. Hal Guetal and students, 2006 February 28; nam_ua395-1.10_38; 107.3 MB 51 Digital Files
    - Business: 3/1/06 @ Noon Standish Room Hugh Johnson / First Albany Corp, 2006 March 2; nam_ua395-1.10_39; 92.5 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Business School: 5/10/06 @ 11:30 AM - 2:00 PM location TBA SofB Awards Ceremony, 2006 May 11; nam_ua395-1.10_40; 179.1 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Business School: 5/10/06 @ 11:30 AM - 2:00 PM location TBA SofB Awards Ceremony, 2006 May 11; nam_ua395-1.10_41; 179.6 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/10/06 @ 6 - 7:30 PM CESTM Rotunda Research Forum, 2006 May 18; nam_ua395-1.10_42; 8.2 MB 4 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/17/06 @ 10:15 AM CC Ballroom Global Class Picture, 2006 May 18; nam_ua395-1.10_43; 23.3 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/17/06 @ 10:15 AM CC Ballroom Global Class Picture, 2006 May 18; nam_ua395-1.10_44; 23.5 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Business: 5/10/06 @ 6 - 7:30 PM CESTM Rotunda Research Forum, 2006 May 18; nam_ua395-1.10_45; 130.2 MB 80 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 11/2/06 from 5:30 - 7:30, Albany Marriott for School of Business Alumni Reception., 2006 November 2; nam_ua395-1.10_46; 255.1 MB 121 Digital Files
    - Development: 11/20/06 @ 3:30 PM School of Business for photo of Dean Paul Leonard, 2006 November 20; nam_ua395-1.10_47; 109.1 MB 55 Digital Files
    - 12/18/06 @ 10:00 a.m. in BA 364 (Dean Leonard's office) for photo of Albina Grignon and Dean Leonard, awarding a School of Business student a gift, for our Connections newsletter., 2006 December 19; nam_ua395-1.10_48; 6.4 MB 8 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 2/16/07 @ 1 - 2 PM BA 313A for two group shots., 2007 February 16; nam_ua395-1.10_49; 286.2 MB 214 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 3/01/07 @ 10 AM Dean's Office School of Business for photo of Paul Leonard., 2007 March 1; nam_ua395-1.10_50; 99.0 MB 177 Digital Files
    - Business: Photo Session on May 7th from 1-4 in the Standish Room. Event is retirement reception for Paul Morgan, Sr., 2007 April 25; nam_ua395-1.10_51; 63.5 MB 146 Digital Files
    - Business: Photo Session on May 7th from 1-4 in the Standish Room. Event is retirement reception for Paul Morgan, Sr., 2007 April 25; nam_ua395-1.10_52; 63.5 MB 146 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 4/26/07 @ 3 - 5 PM Life Science RB (D'Ambra Auditorium) for UAlbany Organization of Women Faculty Open Forum with speaker Dr.Lisa Freehill. Pictures of her and also the participants before the talk and afterwards would be great., 2007 April 26; nam_ua395-1.10_53; 47.9 MB 55 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 5/9/07 @ 12:30 - 1:30 PM Campus Center Ballroom for Awards Luncheon, 2007 May 10; nam_ua395-1.10_54; 51.2 MB 114 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 5/16/07 @ 12 Noon, Fireside Lounge, Campus Center for the School of Business's annual class picture (Class of 2008). There will be 39 students in the picture., 2007 May 17; nam_ua395-1.10_55; 19.4 MB 18 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 5/19 from 6 - 8 PM Standish Room, New Library for Honorary Degree Commencement Dinner Format: brief cocktail time and sit down dinner for ~ 60 (VIPs, O.I.C. & VP's along with other Commencement Platform Party members) w/ some short speeches by Honorary Degree recipients & Susan Herbst, 2007 May 20; nam_ua395-1.10_56; 297.8 MB 74 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 5/19/07 from 11:30 - 12:30 at the Sefcu Arena for candid shots after Graduate Ceremony., 2007 May 20; nam_ua395-1.10_57; 63.7 MB 121 Digital Files
    - School of Business:; 11:30 - 1:30 in Bus. Admin Bldg, room 219 on Aug. 24th. Pictures of new MBA and Accounting students., 2007 August 14; nam_ua395-1.10_58; 845.9 MB 276 Digital Files
    - School of Business: Photos of student athletes at the main entrance of the SEFCU Arena on 8/27/07 from 1:00 - 2:30 p.m., 2007 September 5; nam_ua395-1.10_59; 68.4 MB 171 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: Move-in day photos to include general shots of students moving in, a male and female student laden down with belongings, different ethnicities, Susan Herbt helping out, parents hugging their child, etc. Also, photos of check presentation from Holiday Inn at 10:45 a.m. at State Quad on the steps or under a canopy if rain., 2007 September 5; nam_ua395-1.10_60; 175.5 MB 178 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 10/25/07 from 6 - 8 p.m. at the capitol region Alumni Event located in the UHALL atrium., 2007 September 25; nam_ua395-1.10_61; 72.9 MB 128 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 1/25/08 @ 11 AM - 12:30 PM, BA 313A for group photo and individual head shots., 2008 January 25; nam_ua395-1.10_62; 43.4 MB 125 Digital Files
    - School of Business: Photo session: 5/7/08 in NanoFab North for the Research Forum from 5:30 - 7:30 pm., 2008 May 7; nam_ua395-1.10_63; 386.7 MB 234 Digital Files
    - School of Business: Photo session: 5/7/08 in NanoFab North for the Research Forum from 5:30 - 7:30 pm., 2008 May 7; nam_ua395-1.10_64; 386.7 MB 234 Digital Files
    - School of Business: Photo session: 5/9/08 @ 11 a.m. for a Blue Ribbon Panel of CIO's event at the School of Business., 2008 May 9; nam_ua395-1.10_65; 40.7 MB 56 Digital Files
    - School of Business: 5/14/08 @ 1:30 PM in Campus Center Assembly Hall for class picture of 30 MBA students., 2008 May 14; nam_ua395-1.10_66; 6.9 MB 3 Digital Files
    - SOB_Beer Distribution Game, 2008 August 22; nam_ua395-1.10_67; 33.4 MB 84 Digital Files
    - Accounting Orientation, 2008 August 26; nam_ua395-1.10_68; 67.1 MB 119 Digital Files
    - SOB_future building site ceremony, 2008 October 3; nam_ua395-1.10_69; 79.0 MB 102 Digital Files
    - Women's MBA, 2009 March 11; nam_ua395-1.10_70; 194.1 MB 224 Digital Files
    - School of Business Erns t& Young Check Presentation, 2009 May 1; nam_ua395-1.10_71; 8.5 MB 14 Digital Files
    - Evening MBA Research Forum, 2009 May 7; nam_ua395-1.10_72; 54.6 MB 123 Digital Files
    - School of Business Awards, 2009 May 7; nam_ua395-1.10_73; 74.8 MB 191 Digital Files
    - MBA, 2009 May 14; nam_ua395-1.10_74; 67.2 MB 24 Digital Files
    - SOB Grad Commencement Reception, 2009 May 17; nam_ua395-1.10_75; 53.3 MB 81 Digital Files
    - Dr. Vladimir Sokolov_SoB, 2009 July 22; nam_ua395-1.10_76; 35.0 MB 60 Digital Files
    - SOB_Grad Orientation, 2009 August 28; nam_ua395-1.10_77; 723.4 MB 194 Digital Files
    - Ernst and Young Alumni Check Presentation, 2010 April 29; nam_ua395-1.10_78; 8.7 MB 11 Digital Files
    - SoB and alumn, 2010 May 5; nam_ua395-1.10_79; 6.1 MB 18 Digital Files
    - SoB_Awards Luncheon, 2010 May 5; nam_ua395-1.10_80; 46.8 MB 110 Digital Files
    - Evening MBA Research Forum, 2010 May 5; nam_ua395-1.10_81; 61.6 MB 129 Digital Files
    - SoB_Architectural Design Unveiling, 2010 May 10; nam_ua395-1.10_82; 78.6 MB 184 Digital Files
    - Go Green MBA, 2010 May 12; nam_ua395-1.10_83; 14.2 MB 12 Digital Files
    - SoB_commencement, 2010 May 15; nam_ua395-1.10_84; 36.9 MB 30 Digital Files
  - School of Social Welfare, 2013 October 29-2013 October 29; nam_ua395-1.11; 3.49 GB 2150 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 10/21/02 @ 11:45 AM Times Union Bldg. Wolf Rd. Albany check presentation digital, 2002 November 1; nam_ua395-1.11_1; 73.2 MB 44 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/1/03 @ 11 AM Rockwell Center 421 W. Columbia St. Cohoes, NY Action photo: Students Toni Marion and Melissa Mosley with clients digital, 2003 April 29; nam_ua395-1.11_2; 23.6 MB 55 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: photo shoot: 6/9/03 @ 10:30 PM Milne 200 Hartford Foundation digital, 2003 June 23; nam_ua395-1.11_3; 21.1 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: photo shoot: 6/9/03 @ 10:30 PM Milne 200 Hartford Foundation digital, 2003 June 23; nam_ua395-1.11_4; 21.1 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 6/11/03 @ 9 AM Desmond Hotel Albany Aging Seminar w/ Hartford Foundation digital, 2003 June 25; nam_ua395-1.11_5; 19.4 MB 64 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 6/11/03 @ 9 AM Desmond Hotel Albany Aging Seminar w/ Hartford Foundation digital, 2003 June 25; nam_ua395-1.11_6; 19.4 MB 64 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/18/04 @ 12 Noon Milne 200 Community Forum: Place Based Philanthropy digital, 2004 June 1; nam_ua395-1.11_7; 42.6 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/18/04 @ 12 Noon Milne 200 Community Forum: Place Based Philanthropy digital, 2004 June 1; nam_ua395-1.11_8; 42.6 MB 27 Digital Files
    - School of Social Welfare: 10/5/04 @ 11 AM Richardson 108 various faculty and classroom shots digital, 2004 October 14; nam_ua395-1.11_9; 196.4 MB 127 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 11/13/04 @ 3PM - 7 PM Milne 200 Memorial for Bill Reid digital, 2004 November 15; nam_ua395-1.11_10; 178.2 MB 126 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 11/19/04 @ 12 Noon Draper 147 various locations digital, 2004 November 29; nam_ua395-1.11_11; 174.4 MB 126 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 11/19/04 @ 3 PM Daughters of Sarah Nursing Facility Washington Ave Ext Student volunteers/interns digital, 2004 December 2; nam_ua395-1.11_12; 88.3 MB 53 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 11/19/04 @ 2 PM Milne 200 Wesley Clark digital, 2004 December 6; nam_ua395-1.11_13; 52.5 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 12/9/04 @ 12:30 PM Westview Senior Ctr. Central Ave / Allen St. Students with senior clients digital, 2004 December 21; nam_ua395-1.11_14; 289.1 MB 194 Digital Files